<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Authors | SORBA-Athens | Mountain Biking in Athens</title>
    <link>http://localhost:57219/authors/</link>
      <atom:link href="http://localhost:57219/authors/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Authors</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright> © SORBA-Athens 2020</copyright><lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>http://localhost:57219/img/icon-32.png</url>
      <title>Authors</title>
      <link>http://localhost:57219/authors/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:57219/authors/seth-younger/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:57219/authors/seth-younger/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Seth Younger is the president of SORBA-Athens and has been helping with the Athens chapter since about 2015.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:57219/authors/mike-bradshaw/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:57219/authors/mike-bradshaw/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Mike Bradshaw is the vice president representing Trail Creek Park. He has been volunteering on SORB Athens volunteer project for years and routinely loggs hundreds of volunteer hours a year.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:57219/authors/jason-chandler/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:57219/authors/jason-chandler/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Jason is the vice-president represeting Heritage Park. Jason and his family own and operate Chainbuster Racing and are very active in bike communities throughout the southeast and close to home.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:57219/authors/jay-tibbett/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:57219/authors/jay-tibbett/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Jay is the official point of contact for Hawkes Creek Farm and has been coordinating with the landowner and taking care of the trails out there for years. Jay was the second president of SORBA Athens back when Heritage Park was under construction. He&#39;s seen lots of changes over the years, but he has always loved riding and taking care of the trails at Hawkes Creek. Please contact Jay if you would like to help with trail maintenance at Hawkes Creek, or please go  put some wheels on it!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:57219/authors/howie-davis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:57219/authors/howie-davis/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Howie has been helping maintain local &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.sunshinecycles.com/&#34;&gt;bikes&lt;/a&gt; and trails for decades. His official board role is to act as the liaison for the YMCA/OAES trails, but he does a lot more than that.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:57219/authors/bob-dickson/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:57219/authors/bob-dickson/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Bob is passionate about mountainbiking and is working with cyclists in Morgan County to find opportunites for multi-use trails.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:57219/authors/cara-molloy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:57219/authors/cara-molloy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Cara is pasionate about creating more family friendly places to mountainbike in and around Athens, GA.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:57219/authors/jeff-green/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:57219/authors/jeff-green/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Jeff is from Athens, GA and grew up riding bikes, but is relatively new to mountain biking. Jeff reached out to the board wanting to help and we put him to work triming the trails at Trail Creek Park. Due to his hard work and willingness to help Jeff was nominated and elected to the secretary position and he is eager to contribute to our forward progress.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:57219/authors/aaron-bemis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:57219/authors/aaron-bemis/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Aaron helps wherever he can often by volunteering at events or updating the website.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:57219/authors/elliott-caldwell/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:57219/authors/elliott-caldwell/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Elliott believes in the need for bike transportation on all surfaces and we agree with him. He is the executive director at &lt;a href=&#34;https://georgiabikes.org/&#34;&gt;Georgia Bikes&lt;/a&gt; and is helping us spread the message that all bike routes don&#39;t have to be paved.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:57219/authors/sorba-athens/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:57219/authors/sorba-athens/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;SORBA Athens is a 501(3)c non-profit organization located in Athens, GA focused on increasing access to multi-use trails open to mountain bikes. We are one of &lt;a href=&#34;https://sorba.org/chapters/&#34;&gt;46&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://sorba.org&#34;&gt;Southern Off-Road Bicycle Association (SORBA)&lt;/a&gt; chapters which has over 7000 members and is growing. Our primary mission is to increase access to sustainable trails open to mountain bikes in and around Athens, GA. We partner with land managers and other organizations to advocate for access to facilities and resources to make mountain biking a more accessible sport for everyone, especially beginners and kids. We built and maintain the &lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:57219/#trails&#34;&gt;mountain bike trails&lt;/a&gt; at Heritage Park and Trail Creek Park and help maintain Hawkes Creek Farm and other local trails as much as possible. Soon we will begin construction of a pump track and skills course at Trail Creek Park. With an eye to the future we have an agreement with &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.fireflytrail.com/&#34;&gt;Firefly Trail, Inc.&lt;/a&gt; to build a singletrack trail parallel to the Firefly Trail in the town of Maxey&#39;s and we hope to find more parallel trail opportunities as the Firefly is constructed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please join us at one of our &lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:57219/events/&#34;&gt;events&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:57219/donate/&#34;&gt;donate&lt;/a&gt; to one of our trail funds, see other ways to &lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:57219/get_involved/&#34;&gt;get involved&lt;/a&gt;, or &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:sorbaathens@gmail.com&#34;&gt;contact us&lt;/a&gt; for more details! We&#39;re all volunteers with day jobs and limited time, but we don&#39;t turn down help!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
