<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>recent | SORBA-Athens | Mountain Biking in Athens</title>
    <link>http://localhost:57219/tags/recent/</link>
      <atom:link href="http://localhost:57219/tags/recent/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>recent</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright> © SORBA-Athens 2020</copyright><lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>http://localhost:57219/img/icon-32.png</url>
      <title>recent</title>
      <link>http://localhost:57219/tags/recent/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spring 2020 membership drive</title>
      <link>http://localhost:57219/post/spring_membership_drive_2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:57219/post/spring_membership_drive_2020/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.imba.com/membership-drive-rules&#34;&gt;SORBA&#39;s Spring Membership drive is ongoing until June 30th, 2020&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SORBA&#39;s spring membership drive is underway! We&#39;ve been hard at work maintaining our trails, jumping through hoops to get started building the pump track at Walker Park and advocating for permission to build more mountain biking opportunities FOR YOU!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Join or renew your SORBA membership during the month of May and you are entered to win prize packs from IMBA including trips and bikes (see list below).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;featured.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hawkes Creek Work Day Nov 24th, 2019</title>
      <link>http://localhost:57219/post/hawkes-creek-workday-11-24-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:57219/post/hawkes-creek-workday-11-24-2019/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hawkes Creek work day on Sunday November 24th 2019 at 9:30am.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will do some leaf blowing and raking and maybe some weed eating. Let me know if you are planning to be there. We will meet at the barn in back. Contact me on my cell: 706-338-0011.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.google.com/maps/dir//33.959399,+-83.204632/@33.9670456,-83.4322818,15z/data=!4m2!4m1!3e0&#34;&gt;Directions to the barn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;featured.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A new climbing trail at Walker Park </title>
      <link>http://localhost:57219/post/a_comeback_trail/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:57219/post/a_comeback_trail/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We are building one more trail at Trail Creek Park. It will be a climbing only trail from the bottom of Widespread and Panic back to the top without crossing any roads! After you finish widespread or Panic and pass the rocky shoals the comback trail will turn right and wind all the way back to the top on the smoothest route we could find. Unfortuantely we had to reroute the last turn on panic but the new final turn is even better than ever.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;featured.png#floatleft&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Pump Track at Trail Creek Park is Moving Forward</title>
      <link>http://localhost:57219/post/pump-track-green-light/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:57219/post/pump-track-green-light/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We finally have permission to start buiding the pump track at Trail Creek Park. Along with the dirt donation from New Urban Forestry we are well on our way. Many of the construction steps will be completed at least in part by contractors, but there will be plenty of volunteer work to do so look out for those opportunities going forward. In the meantime we will start building a return trial from the bottom of Widespread and Panic back to the top. The new trail will tentatively be called &amp;lsquo;Comeack Sauce&amp;rsquo;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
